{
    "id": "3944c582c6bf4b54a9c5b228e82d5b55",
    "title": "Frame questions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "94ae7dd9cfe24c76be32a4ca8f98a416",
            "title": "Frame Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "..................................... books are these?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who's",
                        "Whose",
                        "Whos"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... do you want?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Whose",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... will you stay with?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whom",
                        "What",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "With ....................................... are you going?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... did you go there?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Why",
                        "What",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... is your boy?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... do you come from?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "When",
                        "Where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... did you meet him?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "When",
                        "Where",
                        "How",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... long is this bridge?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... old is your father?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... brothers and sisters do you have?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How many",
                        "How much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... is your headmaster?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ did you come to this place?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "When",
                        "Where",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}